Guide to the Andrew Schultz Schultz, Jr. papers, 1932-1991
Schultz, Andrew Schultz, Jr. papers, 1932-1991
- Series IV. Graduate Student Papers, Miscellaneous Industrial Engineering Papers (Boxes 3, 18, 20, 21, 22, 26, 27, 28)
  - Hammer, Kenneth Frederick - Master of Science Thesis, Sept. 1954 (Box 20)
  - Reports and Hand-Drawn Charts, Part I (Box 21)
  - Handwritten Report (Box 21)
  - Farber, Mark - Handwritten Report (Box 21)
  - Webb Institute of Naval Architecture, 1967-1972 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Webb Institute, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Webb Institute - Interim Report, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Logistics Management Institute Report, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Memorandum and reports on major industrial inefficiency, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Reports and hand-drawn charts, part 2 (legal size), 1971-1973 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Center for Maritime Studies final report, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Shipboard manpower, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - U.S. government general account office personal file, parts 1-2, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 17-18)
  - Webb Institute and shipbuilding papers, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Webb Institute papers, 1968-1973 (Box 22, Folder 20-21)
  - Federal Register, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Highway Safety Papers, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Congressional Reports (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Journal of American Insurance, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Accidental Death and Injury Statistics, 1970-72 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Student Reports, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Automotive Crash Injury Research Reports, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Automotive Crash Injury Research Reports (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - ACIR Bulletins, 1962-66 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Reports: Vehicle Interactions on Highways (Box 26, Folder 9a)
  - Automotive Crash Injury Research Reports, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Automotive Crash Injury Research Reports, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Automotive Crash Injury Research Reports, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Automotive Crash Injury Research Reports, 1964-1966 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Automotive Crash Injury Research Reports, 1961-1964 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Automotive Crash Injury Research Reports, 1964-1966 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Automotive Crash Injury Research Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Automotive Crash Injury Research Reports, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Automotive Crash Injury Research Reports, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Report: GMR Traffic Conflicts Technique Procedures Manual, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Martin/Marietta Engineering Report, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Report: "Engineering Aspects of Thermal Discharges to a Stratified Lake," 1969 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - National Science Foundation Report, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Report: "Energy Needs and Environmental Quality," 1971 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Magazine Articles, 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Various Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Newsletters, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Studies of Graduate Engineers (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Report: "The Engineer Today" (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Reports: "Studies in Accident-Injury Prevention" and "The Human Factor in Accidents," 1951, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Studies of University of California Engineering Graduates (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Engineering Educational Trends Committee Report, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - National Conference - Professional Engineering Education, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Symposium: "What Should the National Academy of Engineering do about Engineering Education?" 1966 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Conferences on Engineering Education, 1958, 1964, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Report: "Laboratory-Oriented Studies for Engineering Students," 1968 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Engineering Education, 1966-1968 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Engineering - Funding, Development, 1964-1965 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Engineering Conference Reports, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Engineering Education, cont., 1963-1964 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Engineering, Future of, 1962-1971 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Engineering Education - Reports, Publications, 1964-1968 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Engineering: Research and Development, 1964-1969 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Report: Goals of an Engineering Education, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Engineering Education Reports, 1963-1969 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Engineering Education Reports, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Goals of Engineering Education Reports, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Naval Research, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Science and Technology articles, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Engineering Education: articles, reports, 1965-1967 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Report: "The Engineering Program at Dartmouth College: Contents of the Core Curriculum," 1963 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Study: National Science Foundation - "The Curriculum in Industrial Engineering," 1964-1966 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Journal of Industrial Engineering, 1967 1967 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Mathematics Association of America - Recommendations on the Undergraduate Mathematics Program, 1964-1966 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Study of Industrial Engineering Education, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Study of Industrial Engineering Education (cont.), 1968 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Study of Industrial Engineering Education (cont.), 1966 (Box 27, Folder 28-29)
  - Federal Highway Administration: Automotive Industrial Engineering Study, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Federal Highway Administration Reports, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Federal Highway Administration Reports, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Federal Highway Administration Reports, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Management Software Development Corp. Reports, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Study: "The Manufacturing Engineer Today and Tomorrow" (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Ford Motor Company Report, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 7-8)
  - National Highway Safety Bureau - Automotive Industrial Engineering Study; sections 1 & 2, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 9-10)
  - Auto Safety Expenses, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Auto Industrial Engineering Panel Corp., 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Other Industrial Engineering Reports, 1969, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - World Magazine, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Department of Defense Reports, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Department of Defense Reports, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Study: "To Determine Effect on Desc-E Functions of Certaom Desc Classes are Transferred," 1962 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Revised Concept of Standardization, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Air Force Semiannual Report of Standardization Accomplishments, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Dept. of Defense Standardization Program, 1962-1963 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Armed Forces Supply Support Center Report, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Dept. of Defense Standardization Panel, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 22-23)
  - Report on a Survey of the Defense Standardization Program, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Dept. of Defense Report: Proposed Manual of Instructions for Incorporating Multilevel Reliability Requirements into Part Specificaitons, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Series V. Research and Reports (Boxes 4, 14, 18, 21)
  - Manufacturing Progress Function / Learning Curve Research for Operations Research Office and General Electric - Andrew Schultz, Richard W. Conway, Kenneth F. Hammer 1953-1961 Notes, logbooks, reports, calculations, etc. (Box 4, Folder 1-20)
  - Progress Function Staff Memo, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Progress Function Correspondence, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Progress Function Summary Report, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - General Electric Learning Curve/Progress Function, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Progress Function Miscellaneous, ca. 1961 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Fifth Year Project Report - Pleasant Valley Wine Company, 1955 (Box 4)
  - Fifth Year Project Report - Clapp's Baby Food Project, 1956 Edward L. Weinthaler, Jr. (Box 4)
  - Fifth Year Project Report - SI Handling Systems Inc., Easton PA, 1960 William Sites, Lawrence Teel, Oskar Rogg, Karl Van Wirt, Brooks Helmick, Dan R. Priedeman (Box 4)
  - Fifth Year Project Report - Duffy-Mott Plant Location Project, 1958 R. A. Foisie, C. F. Knight, J. M. Saravia, R. W. Scott, A. E. Suter (Box 4)
  - Fifth Year Project Report - The Hilliard Clutch Corporation, 1956 Harold Abrams, Paul M. Gladstone, Daniel W. Moore, Langston Weinberg (Box 4)
  - Cornell University: Economy Possibilities in the College of Engineering, Report by a Sub-Committee of the General University Committee on Economy, 1950 Carl Crandall, Peter E. Kyle, Kendall C. White, Malcolm S. McIlroy (Box 4)
  - Economic Control of Purchased Inventory Report, 1956 Donald A. Hughes, Joseph R. Varnak (Box 4)
  - "Work Measurement Through Elemental Motion Time Standards," 1951 (Box 4)
  - "Personal Aircraft: An American Appraisal" by T. P. Wright, 1947 (Box 4)
  - Binder of Cornell University Recruiting Information Forms, 1958-1959 (Box 4)
  - Energy, 1964-1977 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - S. C. Hollister, 1940-1977 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Productivity, 1959-1980 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Standardization, L. C., etc., 1963-1977 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Technology and Society, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Unsolved problems, university, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Andover, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - CPT (Chicago Pneumatic Tool Company), 1969-1976 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Holden-Day, Inc., 1961-1971 (Box 14, Folder 9-15)
  - Lexington, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - LMI (Logistics Management Institute), 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 17-18)
  - LMI, part III, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - LMI, parts 1-2, 1963-1966 (Box 14, Folder 20-21)
  - LMI, parts I-II, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 22-23)
  - LMI, parts I-III, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 24-26)
  - Production worker research study conference packet, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories Organizational directory, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Duffy-Mott Company Correspondence, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Morse Chain Company Correspondence, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Shipbuilding Labor Market Information 1969, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Hand written report 1973 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Mark Farber: hand written report (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - A Survey of Waste Evaluation, N. J. Levy and G. C. Raubach 1973 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Pipe Department Information Flow 1973 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Newport News Shipbuilding Company 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Shipbuilding Data and Notes 1957-1973 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Program Control Manual, Vol. I-V 1971 (Box 21, Folder 10-15)
  - Material Management Division Booklet, Tenneco Corp. (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Farber, M. - Writings on Shipbuilding (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Material Support Manual (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Newport News Shipbuilding & Dry Dock Company, Parts I-V 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 19-23)
  - NNS&DD Co.: Summer Survey by Cornell Group (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Newport News Shipbuilding & Dry Dock Company - Evaluation Notes 1973 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Group trace 1973 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Reports and hand-drawn charts, part I (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Series VI. Class of 1936 Reunion Apparel (Box 5)
  - Two White Jackets, Hat, and Button labeled "Mary Schultz" (Box 5)
- Series VII. Biographical Material and Correspondence (Box 6)
  - Biographical Material, 1964-1973 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Publications by and about Schultz, 1970-1972 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Alphabetical, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - A, 1967-1978 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - American Institute of Industrial Engineers, 1971-1974 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - American Institute of Industrial Engineers, 1963-1970 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - B, 1963-1977 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Bangs Memorial, 1985-1991 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Bangs Memorial, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence with Boehringer, 1966-1976 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - C, 1965-1978 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Congratulatory, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Congratulatory (II), 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Convocation - Schultz Professorship Fund, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory, 1966-1977 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Club, 1965-1975 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - D, 1972-1978 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Defense System Management School, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - E, 1964-1978 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Engineering Education and Accreditation Committee, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - F, 1971-1976 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence with Follett, 1964-1972 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence - G, 1965-1977 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence - H, 1963-1979 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Ithaca Staff Purchases, Inc., 1960-1961 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence - J-K, 1965-1976 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence - L, 1967-1977 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence with Lake, 1963-1976 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Lester Knight Scholarship, 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence - M, 1964-1990 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence - N, 1964-1969 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence with Olin, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Opportunities Foregone, 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence - P, 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence with Paskow, 1, 1962-1968 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence with Paskow, 2, 1969-1972 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence with Picha, 1972-1982 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence - R, 1971-1979 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Resignation as Dean, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence with Resler, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence with Rob Roy, 1969-1974 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence - S, 1964-1988 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Stanford Advisory Council, 1969-1973 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Summers Endowment, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence - T-Z, 1964-1978 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Papers, Memos, 1965-1972 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Series VIII. Course Material: Institutes and Programs (Box 7)
  - Course Material, 1, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Course Material, 2 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Projects - Industrial Engineering, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Exams - Qualifying, 1950's (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Engineering - Course 3236; 1, 1950's (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Engineering - Course 3236; 2, 1950's (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Mechanical Engineering - Course 3236 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Engineering - Course 3242: Statistical Control and Sampling Inspection, 1950's (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Mechanical Engineering - Course 3242 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Mechanical Engineering - Course 3242, 1950's (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Course Material - 3247 - Dept. of Industrial and Engineering Administration, 1950's-1960's (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Course Material - 3247 - Dept. of Industrial and Engineering Administration, 1950's (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Mechanical Engineering - Course 3250, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Mechanical Engineering - Course 3254, 1956-1959 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Mechanical Engineering - Course 3280; 1, 1956-1958 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Mechanical Engineering - Course 3280; 2, 1956-1958 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Mechanical Engineering - Course 3292 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Course Material - Graduate School of Business and Public Administration, Outlines and Exams, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Series IX. Institutes and Programs (Boxes 7, 16, 22, 29)
  - Turkish Industrial Management Group; 1, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Turkish Industrial Management Group; 2, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - ILR - Summerbank Executive Training Program - Project Manager's Report, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - ILR - Biglow Institute, 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - ILR - Biglow Institute, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Institute for Effective Teaching, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Graduate Professional Engineering Program, Annual Report, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Consultant: Toronto Institute of Business Administration, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Bell System Executive Conference, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Executive Development Programs: automation, 1953-1959 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - American Institute of Industrial Engineers report, 1955-1956 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Industrial Engineer Group meeting, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Rhee, Tai Wook - Modeling of Process Analysis and its Application to the Shipbuilding Industry, July 20, 1973 1973 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Ingalls Shipbuilding Division GAO Review - Part I, 1972 1972 (Box 22, Folder 24?-25?)
  - New Panel Shop and Blast-Paint Facilities at the Sparrows Point Yard, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 26?)
  - Boehringer Report - Patient Care Unit Planning Evaluation, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Lavigne Report - Patient Traffic Flows to the Dept. of Radiology, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Boehringer Report: Return on Investment Implications of Hostpital Facilities Design, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Mayo Clinic Correspondence, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Medical Systems Reports, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Boehringer - NY Hospitals, 1969-1972 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Boehringer - NY Hospitals, 1969-1972 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - American Management Association (AMA) Study - Gaining Acceptance for Major Methods Changes, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Industrial Engineering Reports - GE, Procter & Gamble (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Hotel Management Talk - Work Simplification (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Rochester - American Society for Quality Control (ASQC) Talk, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Baltimore Symposium on Operations Research (OR) Education, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Rochester Talk - "Keeping Pace with Industrial Engineering," 1956 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - ASQC Talk, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Western Electric Company Simulation (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - OR Related to Production Engineering - Talk by ASQC, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - ASQC - Poughkeepsie, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - ASQC - Corning, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Rochester Quality Control Clinic, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Costs for Decision (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Western Electric Talk, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - American Association of Industrial Engineers (AIIE) Long Range Planning Committee I.E. System Talk - Atlanta, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Cornell Society of Engineers, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - IBM, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - IBM Methods Talk - Poughkeepsie, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - IBM - Advanced Sales Class for Manufacturing Industries, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - IBM - Poughkeepsie, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Rochester AIIE, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - AIIE - Southern Tier - Ithaca, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Rochester QC Clinic, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - AIIE Northeast Regional Conference, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - AIIE Work Measurement Symposium, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - ILR Extension Meeting, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Syracuse - Operations & Management Research Society of NY, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Ithaca IE Series, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Washington D.C. AIIE, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Johns Hopkins University Talk, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - ILR Lab Management, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Info Talks - Parents; Guidance Counselors; Freshmen, 1965-74 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Info Talks - Parents; Guidance Counselors; Freshmen, 1965-74 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Columbus AIIE, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - American Society for Engineering Education - Purdue, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - ILR Seminar, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - IE Seminar, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - ASQC - Binghamton, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - AIIE - Atlanta, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - ASQC - Ithaca, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - ILR, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - National Conference on Creative Engineering Education, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - AIIE - Toronto, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 50)
  - Cornell "Looking Ahead" Conference, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - AIIE - Winston-Salem, NC, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 52)
  - Social Implications of Technology, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 53)
  - IEEE Education Committee Meeting, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 54)
  - Kansas State U. Talk, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 55)
  - SUNY Albany - Conference on Engineering Education and Environmental Problems, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 56)
  - E106 - "Engineering Perspectives," 1972 (Box 29, Folder 57)
  - AIIE Talks, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 58)
  - Production and Engineering, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 59)
  - Cornell IE Seminars, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 60)
  - Industrial Conference, 1949 (Box 29, Folder 61)
  - IE Seminar Papers, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 62)
  - Seminar - Hustling Letters, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 63)
  - Special Conference Letters, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 64)
- Series X. Committees (Box 7, 8, 11)
  - Mechanical Engineering Curriculum Committee, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1938-1942 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Curriculum Committee, Late 1940's (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Committee on 5-year Curriculum, 1948-1953 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Committee - Buildings and Properties; 1, 1957-1968 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Committee - Buildings and Properties; 2, 1968-1970 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Engineering Policy Committee, October 1959-October 20, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Engineering Policy Committee, October 23, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Engineering - Faculty Meeting and College Council Meeting Minutes and Memos; 1, 1970's (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Engineering - Faculty Meeting and College Council Meeting Minutes and Memos; 2, 1970's (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - University Computing Board, April-August 1979 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - University Computing Board, January-March 1979 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - University Computing Board, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Engineering Graduate Committee 1955-1960 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Series XI. Budget Matters (Boxes 8, 11)
  - Budget, 1952-1961 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Budget, 1939-1951 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Budget 1962-63 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Budget 1964-65 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Budget 1965-66 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Budget 1966-67 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Budget 1967-68 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Series XII. Engineering College: Reports, Proposals, Rosters, Photographs (Boxes 8, 11, 13, 19, 20, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35)
  - New Building Planning, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Proposal - Operations Research/Industrial Engineering Laboratory (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Report on Adequacy and Standards of Engineering Curricula (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - "Some Problem Areas in Engineering Administration" (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Department of Administrative Engineering - Business Statistics, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Affiliate Programs, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Technical Resources in Engineering (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Students Registration, 1933-1942 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Students - Administrative Engineers Roster, 1932-1943 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Appointments, 1932-1961 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Cornell Engineers - Salaries, 1954-1972 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Photographs - Faculty (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - History of Engineering at Cornell, 1945-1960 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - "Sibley School Bulletin", 1947 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Newsletter - American Society for Engineering Education, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Publications regarding Engineering at Cornell, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Engineering Design Education at Cornell, Proposal (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Engineering College Plans (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Industrial Engineering planning projection (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Engineering College Administration, Part 1 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Enginnering College Administration, Part 2 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Legislation, Policies, Precedents, Mar. 15, 1971 1971 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Ford grant, parts 1-2 1961-1970 (Box 13, Folder 24-25)
  - Annual report research 1963-1965 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Planning 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Teaching effectiveness 1966-1969 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Financial Management Training Course, Aug. 1957 1957 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Cost Structures (Box 19, Folder 2)